Finding Aid for the Poster Collection LSC.0095
UCLA Library Special Collections
- Barrie's Sentimental Tommy, in Scribner's [New York]., 1895?; 1 poster. 44 × 32 cm. (Box 72)
  An advertisement for the magazine publication of Barrie's novel which began publication serially in Scribner's Magazine, vol.19, January 1896. The poster is based upon a portrait photograph of Barrie by F. Hollyer used at the beginning of the serialization.
- Weston, Edward, 1886-1958. Exhibit poster. Exhibit held, January 29-March 30, 1975.; 2 items. (Box 72)
  Poster for exhibit at The Museum of Modern Art, New York.
- William H. Schab Gallery, Incorporated, New York. Exhibit poster. Exhibit held, October 6-December 8, 1978.; 1 item. (Box 72)
  Engravings and etchings from 16th-18th century.
- World Cup USA 94. Design preview., 1 item. 26 wide × 37.75 high. (Box 73)
  The poster is a guide to the planning and development of World Cup USA 1994 graphic applications. The look is made up of a color palette, symbols, typefaces and action figures.
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 1)
  (Subject entry for European War)
  - France toujours! / France quand même! / Car la France est eternelle, et rien de ce qui est la France ne saurait périr. [S.l.]: Demoulin Frères. SC., [19--] (Paris: Editions Delandre)., 1 print: color; 117 x 49 cm. (Box 1)
    English translation of title: "France always! France through it all! For France is eternal and could never perish." With accompanying black and white numbered image key (separate sheet, dimensions: 32.5 x 50 cm). Signed in lower left of image: "G. FRAIPONT". Printer device in lower left: quill and a sword forming an 'x' in back of a pot of fire. Below image in center: "deposé".
  - Pour le drapeau! Pour la victoire! / Souscrivez á l'Emprunt National / Les Souscriptions sont reçues à Paris et en Province à la Banque National de Crédit. [Paris?: s.n.], 1917 (Paris: Devambez Imp.)., 1 print: color; 120 x 78 cm. (Box 1)
    English translation of title: "For the flag! For victory! Subscribe to the National Loan." Signed in lower right of image:: "GEORGES SCOTT 1917". Stamp in lower left of image: "3ème Emprunt National / Affiche editée par la Banque National de Crédit". In lower right of image: "VISA_No. 9.498". Handwritten on back: "Scott 3em".
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 7)
  - L'Emprunt de la Paix. Paris: Maquet Gr, [1920?]., 1 print: color; 113 x 79 cm. (Box 7)
    Signed in lower right of image: "Le Basque". On back upper left: "Char Boyer". From a painting by Lebasque entitled 'Maternite' (from LC record).
  - Novelty / ciné-concert des Allies / Tous les jours matinée et soirée dimanches et fêtes 2 matinées: a 2H et 4H.1/2 / Entrée permanente / 19, Rue le Peletier / "A deux pas du Boul.d des Italiens" / "American-Bar." Paris: Atel. Delattre et Cie, [191-]., 1 print: color; 119 x 80 cm. (Box 7)
    Signed in lower left of image: "Dola". Rectangular adhesive price stamp (with a circular ink stamp on it) at top in the 'N' pictures a French coin and reads: "Affiches 20c&2/10 P. Tasset". At bottom right: "VISA: 13876". Handwritten on back upper left: "Char Boyer".
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 8)
  - 4e Emprunt de la Défense Nationale. Paris: Imp. Champenois, [1918?]., 1 print: color; 80 x 114 cm. (Box 8)
    English translation of title: "Fourth National Defense Loan." Signed under image at right: "Abel Faivre". LC has this poster and variant of same image but different text.
  - Debout dans la tranchée que l'aurore éclaire, le soldat rêve à la victoire et à son foyer. Pour qu'il puisse assurer l'une et retrouver l'autre, souscrivez au 3e. Emprunt de la Défense Nationale. Paris; Nancy: Berge Levrault, imp., [1917]., 1 print: color; 113 x 79 cm. (Box 8)
    Signed in lower right of image: "Liet. Jean Droit-226". On soldier's collar: "226". Date from LC record.
- World War I--France., 3 items. (Box 76)
  - "La Marseillaise" crée à Strasbourg par Rouget de l'Isle en 1792 y rentre triomphement, en 1918, à la tête des Armées Alliées! 'Allons donc enfants de la Patrie allons chercher de libérer les peuples... (G. Clemenceau).' Paris: Devambez Imp., [1918]., 1 print: color; 119 x 81 cm. (Box 76)
    Signed in lower right of image: 'Jacques Carlu'. In lower left: "VISA 12.498". LC has an alternate version with the same image but different text. Date from LC record.
  - Journée Nationale des Tuberculeux / Anciens militaires / Sauvons-les. Paris: Devambez Imp., [1917]., 1 print: color; 119 x 80 cm. (Box 76)
    Signed in lower right of image: "Abel Faivre". In stamp at lower left edge of image: "cette affiche, destinée à être apposée, ne peut être ni cédée, ni vendue; il est formellement interdit de la détourner de son objet." A special national day for the benefit of veterans who were suffering from tuberculosis (from LC record). Date from LC record.
  - La journée du Poilu. Paris: I. Lapina. Imp. Edit., 1915., 1 print: color; 118 x 80 cm. (Box 76)
    Medallions on both sides of title. Left one reads: 25 Décembre 26 Décembre 1915 Le Poilu. Right one has image of a soldier head in profile (Poilu?) in front of a female statue head in profile with the words 'Le Poilu' underneath. Under title in center of image is a close-up of a notecard which presumably came with the package the soldier in the image is opening. It reads: "Avec vous et par vous nous jourons de sauver la France. Leon Gambetta." Signed in lower right of image: "L. Jonas". Léon Gambetta (1838-1882) was one of the founders of the Third Republic and was regarded as one of the heroes of the Franco-Prussian War of 1870-71. He became premier of France for a short while in 1881 (from LC record).
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 75)
  - Comité d'assistance en Alsace-Lorraine / Tombola Artistique / Tableaux, objets d'art, autographes / Plus de 200 lots offerts par les artistes, hommes de lettres, musiciens, contemporain / 9500 billets; un lot garanti à chaque groupe de 50 billets / Prix de billet: 5 Francs / Exposition du 7 au 30 Avril 1916 au Musée des Arts Decoratifs Pavillon de Marsan, 107, Rue de Rivoli / Prix d'entrée de l'Exposition: 0f 50c. Nancy: Lithographie Berger-Levrault, 1916., 1 print: color; 115 x 80 cm. (Box 75)
    Stamp in lower right: "BILLETS au Siège Social 23, Rue d'Artois, 23". Stamp in text below word Alsace-Lorraine: "23 RUE ARTOIS"
  - Un dernier effort et on l'aura. Paris: Imp. Cornille & Serre, [1918]., 1 print: color; 116 x 80 cm. (Box 75)
    In lower right: "VISA 13.625". Date from LC record.
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 6)
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 5)
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 4)
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 3)
  - On ne passe pas! / 1914 1918 / Par deux fois j'ai tenu et vaincu sur la Marne, / Civil, mon frère, / la sournoise offensive de la "paix blanche" va t'assaillir a ton tour, / Comme moi, tu dois tenir et vaincre, sois fort et malin. / Méfie-toi de l'hypocrisie boche. [S.l.]: Union des Grandes Associations Françaises Contre la Propogande Ennémie, 1918 (Paris: Devambez)., 1 print: color; 114 x 80 cm. (Box 3)
    Signed in lower right of image, under soldier's foot: "Maurice Neumont 1918". In lower left next to printer: "VISA No. 13.037". Poison gas was first used in WWI. The phrase 'they shall not pass' is said to have originated with General Robert Nivelle (1856-1924) at the battle of Verdun in 1916 (from LC record). LC has 1917 edition of this poster, artist's signature is different.
  - Pour la France versez votre or / L'or combat la victoire. Paris: Devambez Imp., [1915]., 1 print: color; 119 x 80 cm. (Box 3)
    Signed in lower left of image: "Abel Faivre". Handwritten on back: "Cha. Boyer". At lower left: "Edité par la societé des amis des artistes". On perimeter of coin: "Liberté - Egalité - Fraternité - 1915".
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 2)
  - 4e Emprunt de la Défense Nationale. Paris: Imp. Champenois, [1918?]., 1 print: color; 80 x 114 cm. (Box 2)
  - Debout dans la tranchée que l'aurore éclaire, le soldat rêve à la victoire et à son foyer. Pour qu'il puisse assurer l'une et retrouver l'autre, souscrivez au 3e. Emprunt de la Défense Nationale. Paris; Nancy: Berge Levrault, imp., [1917]., 1 print: color; 113 x 79 cm. (Box 2)
- World War I--France., 2 items. (Box 9)
- World War I--France (1), Britain (1)., 2 items. (Box 39)
  - On les aura ... po-[?] ... l'act[ion?] ... [S.l.: s.n., 191-]., 1 print: color; 136 x 81 cm. (Box 39)
    Signed: "G.(or H. or F.) Lammiol"? Small red circle in lower right: "5c"
- World War I--France (17), U.S. (36)., 53 items. (Box 18)
  - "It is a remarkable story" said President Wilson ... [S.l.]: War Council of the American Red Cross, [191-]., 1 print: 2 color (black and red); 53 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Text only with Red Cross emblem underneath. International chapters of the American Red Cross listed at end of text. At lower right: "Bulletin No. 5 -- issued by the War Council of the American Red Cross to tell the story of Red Cross activities to the American people."
  - "The Child at Your Door" / 400,000 orphans starving no state aid available / Campaign for $30,000,000 / American Committee relief in the Near East Armenia - Greece - Syria - Persia / 1 Madison Ave. New York ~ Cleveland H. Dodge Treas. New York: American Committee relief in the Near East, [1917] (New York: American Lithographic Co.)., 1 print: 2 color (black and gray); 52 x 35 cm. (Box 18)
    Unidentified artist's monogram under girl's right elbow: "HP"(?). DPP logo (Committee on Public Information, Division of Pictorial Publicity) at lower right of image. Date from LC record.
  - "The time has come to conquer or submit." -- "For us there is but one choice. We have made it" -President Wilson / Buy a Bond of the 2nd Liberty Loan and help win the war / A Liberty Bond is a United States Government Bond. New York: American Lithographic Co., [1917]., 1 print: color; 76 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    In bottom left: "No. 8"
  - Answer the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call / All you need is a heart and a dollar. [Washington, D.C.?]: Committee on Public Information Division of Pictorial Publicity, [1918] (Chicago: Edwards & Deutsch Litho. Co.)., 1 print: color; 70 x 50 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right: "Ray Greenleaf." Dimensions approximated.
  - Caring for the families of America's fighting men ... [S.l.]: War Council of the American Red Cross, [191-]., 1 print: 2 color (red and black); 51 x 34 cm. (Box 18)
    Text only with black decorative border and large Red Cross emblem at bottom center. Also at bottom: "Bulletin no.1, issued by th War Council of the American Red Cross to show the American people how their generous contributions are being expended in the interest of humanity."
  - Civilians when we go through this we need all the help and comfort you can give / The Jewish Welfare Board / United War Work Campaign -- Week of November 11 -- 1918. New York: Alco-Gravure, Inc., 1918., 1 print: 2 color (brown and blue); 84 x 56 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in bottom of image: "Signey H. Riesenberg." Star of David under upper title.
  - Clear - the - way - !! / Buy Bonds / Fourth Liberty Loan. [Washington, D.C.?: Liberty Loan Committee?, 1918] (Boston: Forbes)., 1 print: color; 76 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower left: "Howard Chandler Christy." At bottom left: "10-B."
  - Come on! Buy more Liberty Bonds. Cincinnati, Oh.: Strobridge Litho. Co., 1918., 1 print: color; 74 x 50 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right: "WALTER WHITEHEAD." At bottom left: "8R."
  - Do not relax your efforts / Slackening effort aids the enemy ... / Julius C. Gunter Governor of Colorado. [Colorado?]: State Council of Defense Department of Publicity and Information, 1918 ([S.l.]: American Printing & Publishing Co.)., 1 print: color; 61 x 37 cm. (Box 18)
    Text only with double border of blue then red. Colorado state seal in lower right.
  - Don't fail to visit the Conservation Shop 724 Eighteenth Street Phone Champa 5798 / All work is done there by women and for women whose incomes have been impaired by the war / Handmade laces.... / Headquarters of the Home Relief Committee of the Women's Council for Defence of Colorado and for Denver. [Denver, Colo.?: Home Relief Committee of the Women's Council for Defence of Colorado and for Denver?, 191-]., 1 print: 1 color (black); 36 x 29 cm. (Box 18)
  - Don't let up / keep on saving food. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [1918] ([S.l.]: Wynkoop Hallenbeck Crawford Co.)., 1 print: color; 54 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in top right of image: "F. Luis Mora". USFA logo at lower left of image. DPP logo (Committee on Public Information, Division of Pictorial Publicity) at the right of the standing soldier's foot. At bottom left: "No. 29". Date from LC record.
  - Don't stop saving food. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [191-] (New York: M.B. Brown P'T'G & BDG. Co.)., 1 print: 1 color (blue); 54 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    At bottom left corner: "30b". USFA logo at bottom. Stamps used on back read: "Keep your W.S.S. pledge." (War Savings Stamps)
  - E-e-e-yah-yip / Go over with U.S. Marines. [S.l.: s.n., 191-]., 1 print: color; 71 x 54 cm. (Box 18)
    Artist's monogram to the lower right of soldier.
  - Eight million patriotic Red Cross workers have made 291,004,000 necessary articles for war purposes ... [S.l.]: War Council of the American Red Cross, [1918?]., 1 print: 2 color (black and red); 53 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Text with portrait illustration of nurse at top. Signed under illustration: "DEXTER." At bottom under text: "Bulletin no. 9 -- issued by the War Council of the American Red Cross to show the people of America how their generous contributions are being expended in the interest of humanity. Post in a conspicuous place -- A.S. Burleson, Postmaster General." LC has variant poster with same portrait illustration (POS - US .D485, no. 1). Date from LC record.
  - Follow the pied piper / Join the United States School Garden Army. Washington, D.C.: The Graphic Company, [1919?]., 1 print: color; 56 x 41 cm. (Box 18)
    Bag and hat on children say "USSG". Stamps used on back read: "Keep your W.S.S. pledge" (War Savings Stamps). Artist could also be: Macinel Wright Enright (ref. Borkan). Date from LC record.
  - For the safety of womanhood, for the protection of childhood, for the honor of manhood, and for liberty throughout the world, help 'till it hurts. Washington, D.C.: Liberty Loan Committee, [1918], 1 print: color; 51 x 33 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in bottom of image: "DARFOUR-KER(?)" Image caption: "From the Delineator, April, 1918 issue."
  - Have you a Red Cross Service Flag? [S.l.]: American Red Cross, 1918; (Chicago: Edwards & Deutsch Litho. Co.)., 1 print: color; 70 x 53 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in left side of window sill: "JESSIE WILLCOX SMITH."
  - Hunger / For three years America has fought starvation in Belgium / Will you eat less wheat meat fats and sugars that we may still send food in ship loads? [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [191-]., 1 print: 2 color (red and black); 74 x 54 cm. (Box 18)
    At lower left: "No.12." USFA emblem at bottom.
  - I summon you to comradeship (Woodrow Wilson's signature) / Answer the Red Cross Christmas Roll Call for universal membership. [S.l.: American Red Cross], 1918 (New York: U.S. Prtg. & Lith. Co.)., 1 print: color; 70 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right of image: "MIELZINER (LM monogram) 1918." Red Cross emblem at bottom left. "43" handwritten on verso in brown and below it in red.
  - Invest! [S.l.: s.n., 1919]., 1 print: 2 color (red and blue); 61 x 60 cm. (Box 18)
    At bottom left: "V-306."
  - Jan. 30th Tag you shovel day / Has your coal shovel been tagged yet? [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Fuel Administration, [191-], 1 print: 2 color (black and orange); 48 x 32 cm. (Box 18)
    Tag on shovel reads: "Save that shovelful of coal a day for Uncle Sam." Effort emblem at bottom center.
  - Join -- all you need is a heart and a dollar. [S.l.: Red Cross, 191-], 1 print: 2 color (black and red); 51 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Text with large Red Cross emblem. LC has poster with same title but with nurse portrait illustration (POS - US .D485, no. 1).
  - June 28th pledge day for war savings / Uncle Sam to Colorado..."You've never failed me yet!" Denver, Colo.: Brock Haffner Press, [1918], 1 print: color; 53 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed at bottom: "Engravings by Cocks-Clark." Around title: "blue banner with yellow symbol hanging over border. Cocks-Clark: W.A. Cocks and H.M. Clark. Through their collaboration, they gained entry into Denver's printing industry as Cocks-Clark Engraving in 1906 and became distinguished as the largest supplier of copper and brass engraved plates in the region. Company is now: Cocks-Clark Graphics, Inc. (from cocks-clark website: www.cocksclark.com).
  - June 28th Pledge Day for War Savings / W.S.S. / How many $5 War Savings Stamps will you promise to buy before Dec. 31st 1918? Denver, Colo.: Brock-Haffner Press, 1918., 1 print: color; 53 x 71 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in bottom right of image: "Cocks-Clark Denver." At bottom: "Engravigs by Cocks-Clark."
  - June 28th the dawn of a new era in American history! The era of complete self-denial and united effort to win the war. Every day, every hour consecrated to working and saving for this great purpose. [Washington, D.C.?]: USFA, [1918] (Denver, Co.: Brock-Haffner Press), 1 print: color; 53 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed at bottom-center: "Cocks-Clark." Decorative border with USFA emblem also at bottom-center. Cocks-Clark: W.A. Cocks and H.M. Clark. Through their collaboration, they gained entry into Denver's printing industry as Cocks-Clark Engraving in 1906 and became distinguished as the largest supplier of copper and brass engraved plates in the region. Company is now: Cocks-Clark Graphics, Inc. (from cocks-clark website: www.cocksclark.com).
  - Keep it coming / "We must not only feed our soldiers at the front but the millions of women and children behind our lines" Gen. John J. Pershing / Waste nothing. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [191-] (New York: W.F. Powers Litho. Co.)., 1 print: color; 70 x 50 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in top left: "ILLIAN." At lower left: "No.14." USFA emblem at lower left. Dimensions approximated.
  - Lest they perish / Campaign for $30,000,000 / American Committee for relief in the Near East Armenia - Greece - Syria - Persia / One Madison Ave., New York Cleveland H. Dodge, Treasurer. New York: American Committee for relief in the Near East, [1917] (New York: Conwell Graphic Companies)., 1 print: color; 46 x 31 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower left of image: "W. B. King" (artist/designer name from LC record). Date from LC record.
  - Life in the Navy / Food for fighters / Sea fighters must have A-1 stuff and the American Navy is the best fed in the world. Before taken on board ship, every ounce of meat is inspected ... Come in for fighting and big eats and enlist in the Navy. New York: Press of U.S. Navy Recruiting Bureau, [191-]., 1 print: b&w photomontage; 35 x 43 cm. (Box 18)
    On left and right sides under photos: "U.S.N.". Two Navy logos under center photos. Lower center photo reads: "Daily Navy Ration".
  - L'Italia ha bisogno di carne-frumento-grasso & zucchero / Mangiate poco di questo cibo perché deve andare al nostro popolo, e le truppe d'Italia. [S.l.]: Amministrazione d[e] Cibi Stati Uniti, [1917] (Brooklyn, NY: Latham Litho. & Ptg. Co.)., 1 print: color; 71 x 52 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right of image: "Illion". Title translated: Italy needs meat, wheat, fat, and sugar. Date from LC record.
  - Little Americans Do your bit Eat Oatmeal - Corn meal mush - Hominy - other corn cereals - and Rice with milk. Save the wheat for our soldiers. Leave nothing on your plate. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [1917]., 1 print: color; 53 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right of illustration roundel at top. USFA logo at bottom center. "No. 21" at lower left corner. Date from LC record.
  - Make our American Red Cross in peace as in war / "The Greatest Mother in the World" / Third Red Cross Roll Call Nov. 2-11, 1919. [Wahington, D.C.?: American Red Cross?], 1919., 1 print: color; 76 x 49.5 cm. (Box 18)
    Illustration after Alonzo Earl Foringer (see variant poster).
  - Mr. Hoover requests: Consume stuff nearest to point of production. This avoids transportation congestion and will help win the war! / U.S. Exposition -- Denver April 5th to 12th 1918! Denver, Colo.: Union Printing and Publishing Co., 1918., 1 print: 2 color (red and black); 53 x 70 cm. (Box 18)
    U.S. emblem reads: "Buy goods made in Colorado." The top corners patched with contemporaneous U.S. Exposition stamps.
  - Navy! Uncle Sam is calling you / Enlist in the Navy! / Recruiting Station / "I want you in the Navy and I want you now." New York: Leslie Judge Co., 1917 (Los Angeles, Ca.: Western Litho. Co)., 1 print: color; 74 x 53 cm. (Box 18)
    Illustration after James Montgomery Flagg. In lower right: "Reprinted by request from Leslie's Preparedness number July 6, 1916."
  - Navy! Uncle Sam is calling you! Enlist in the Navy! Do it now! I want you. New York: Leslie-Judge Co., 1917., 1 print: color; 36 x 27 cm. (Box 18)
    Bottom right: "Reprinted by Request from Leslie's Preparedness Number July 6, 1916.
  - Order coal now. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Fuel Administration, [191-] (Chicago: Edwards & Deutsch Litho. Co.), 1 print: color; 75 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower left: "J.C. Leyendecker."
  - Order your coal now / Get it out of Uncle Sam's way -- he needs the railroads for the war. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Fuel Administration, [191-] (New York: United States Prtg. & Lith. Co.)., 1 print: 2 color (orange and black); 70 x 53 cm. (Box 18)
    At bottom left and right: U.S. Fuel Admin. Save that Shovelful emblems. At bottom center: "fgc."
  - Our flags Beat Germany / Support every flag that opposes Prussianism / Eat less of the food fighters need / Deny yourself something / Waste nothing. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [1918] (Chicago: Edwards & Deutsch Litho. Co.)., 1 print: color; 54 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right: "Adolph Treidler". USFA logo under text. In lower left corner: "OB." (A horizontal version of this poster was also produced.) Date from LC record.
  - Our service creed [text blocks]. [S.l.: Red Cross, 191-]., 1 print: 2 color (black and red); 56 x 36 cm. (Box 18)
    Text only with a small Red Cross emblem at top. Artist's signature at bottom left of image: "J.M.R." (may be J.M.H.)
  - President's War Savings Proclamation [text blocks] / Governor's War Savings Proclamation [text blocks]. Denver, Colo.: Brock Haffner Press, 1918., 1 print: 1 color (blue); 41 x 56 cm. (Box 18)
    Text only.
  - Remember Belgium / Buy Bonds / Fourth Liberty Loan. [Washington, D.C.?: Liberty Loan Committee?, 1918] (New York: United States Printing and Lithograph Co.)., 1 print: color; 76 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    At bottom left: "6-B." Date from Rawls.
  - See him through / Help us to help the boys / National Catholic War Council Knights of Columbus / United War Work Campaign -- Week of November 11 -- 1918. [S.l.]: National Catholic War Council, 1918 (New York: American Lithographic Co.)., 1 print: color; 76 x 51 cm. (Box 18)
    Signed in lower right of image: "BURTON RICE." National Catholic War Council emblem at lower left. Date from LC.
  - Sugar means ships / The consumption of sugar sweetened drinks must be reduced / For your beverages 400 million lbs. of sugar were imported in ships last year. Every ship is needed to carry soldiers and supplies now. [Washington, D.C.?]: United States Food Administration, [1917] (New York: The Carey Printing Company)., 1 print: 1 color (black); 39 x 48 cm. (Box 18)